A sound soul dwells within a sound mind, and a sound body.
A bomb, huh?
Over there! Look it!
Huh?
I've arranged at random, without any symmetry. Absolutely disgusting.
I heard an explosion.
It must be one of the tadpole bombs I set. We need to hurry!
I smell something.
Yes. We're almost there now. The Kishin is just ahead.
You fools, I'm the one who's leading. Things are going to get interesting now.
Hey, man!
繋いだ魂の火が胸を刺すなら 言葉よりもっと強い響きが今聞こえるか
Six人目も合わさず運命まで絡んでく
行き先もらったポテル食えない夜の端で
不可愛しすぎた眩しさが悪い夢に続いても
繋いだ魂の火が胸を刺すなら
言葉よりもっと強い響きが今聞こえるか
出会った理由は途絶びに突きつけられて
触れた瞬間の傷の分だけ確かになれる
It's an abomination
Such an inconsistent arrangement is unconscionable
Damn it
Hey kid, let's forget about consistency for now
We can pass right on through
Just don't look at them for too long
It's starting to make me sick
That would feel good
See?
What did I tell you?
Okay
In your defense, I suppose poorly arranged bombs are as terrifying to you
as a path full of monsters would be to most normal people
You know, it might not just be the whole inconsistent arrangement thingy
Those are bombs after all
Who wouldn't be scared?
Yeah, it's possible you got a point there
This trap may be the end of me
It's over
Whoa, hold on just a sec
Vacation's gonna wake back up if you give up this easily
You're a reaper
If you can't do this, then who can?
You can say whatever you want
I'm nothing but filthy reaper scum
Just put me by the curb on garbage day
It's your turn, Patty
Tell him in that special way that you have
Okay
Get your ass moving now, damn you
Nice
He's using the blast to give himself more momentum
Well done
You did an incredible job of finally getting his butt moving, Patty
Amazing
Yeah, it was really scary, wasn't I, sis?
Dammit, Patty, I hate you so much
I really, really hate you
Hang in there
It's just going to be a little bit longer
Something's following us at breakneck speed
And it's catching up
Free, we've got to inject the black blood into the Kishin
If anything happens to this case before we do
Then Medusa's going to slaughter us both
I know she will, but I've got an idea
Let me borrow that tadpole you're riding on
I'm gonna need it
Huh?
Tadpole Jackson?
What are you gonna do with him?
Not much
Just get a jump on the enemy
May my soul reach you
A dry heart inside unbearable isolation
Let's go
It's all just so funny, you know?
Quit it
Please stop
You're all wobbly and giggly
I don't like it
Stay away from me
I told you
I hate wobbly giggle
That's too bad
I don't like him
Hey, it's black
It's so pretty
What's with this?
She's really lost it now
Go on, hurt me some more
You can do better than this, can't you?
So this is madness
It protects your partner from feeling any fear
Her soul and her opponent's soul are irrelevant
They have nothing to do with this fight
Come on, give me something new
Can't you do anything like eye gouging or fish hooking?
No?
Well, maybe you'd like to tear off my tongue
What are you doing out there, Maka?
Getting your tongue torn off was not part of the plan, remember?
Damn it
Now I'm getting pulled into the madness, too
Hurry, Maka
Or you won't ever be able to come back
Soul
Oh, wow
That's embarrassing
It's not that different from how you normally are
Now hurry up and do whatever you need to do
Yeah, I'm working on it
I think I can do this
I had a weird kind of premonition when I was sane
Now that I've got the same madness as Corona
I can match our soul wavelengths and find out what it is
Feel it
Look at this
This is my soul
It really is pretty tiny
Another one
It's not in the best shape
A little twisted, a bit worse for the wear
Kind of rough around the edges, too
But it's always there for me
This is my soul eater soul
Now where's Krona's soul?
That must be his soul up there
It's hard to explain
But I'm sensing a very dry wavelength
A desert?
It almost looks like it could be a beach
But with no ocean
Krona?
I'm gonna make you pay for this
He was my food slave
Um pumpkin pumpkin
Pumpkin pumpkin
Would you like some more?
It's important for a lady to be limber and flexible
Five against one
And there's not a scratch on my perfect body
They could use some practice
The newly stabbed up
And there's a slap
Chichi
Chee
I wouldn't get too cocky if I were you, little kitty.
Don't you know that the cornered rat will bite the cat?
Hot, hot, hot, hot!
Do you think I'm going to let you get away with trying to seduce men on my turn?
Oh, oh, oh, no.
I can't take anymore.
You're going to be one dead feline.
Big talk coming from a quintuple-decker mousy.
Huh, what a distasteful outfit.
Like you're really one to talk.
Isn't this top a little drafty?
Didn't you die or something?
At long last, the Black Blood is ready.
All that remains now is to inject it into the Kishin and revive it.
You can keep struggling as long as you want, but it's no use.
My plan is going to succeed no matter what.
Tell me.
If you do get your way and the Kishin is revived, what will happen to the Demon Sword child?
Your Black Blood research is complete.
You're done with the experiment for which you needed this child.
So now?
Oh, please.
What am I going to do with it?
Let's see.
I ordered it around all its life, so now it's lacking in independence.
One reason not to be an overbearing mother, I suppose.
Anyway, Corona didn't turn out well.
It was a failure of mine.
Lacking independence or not, he's your kid.
What are you going to do with him?
What will you do with your child?
Quit laughing.
What's got you two so irritated?
You sound ridiculous.
Do I really have to tell you what you already know?
Think about it this way.
Why would I keep something that I no longer need?
It makes much more sense to throw it away.
But why do you ask?
Do you want it?
You can have my hand-me-downs if you like.
You could use it for your experiments or something.
You evil witch.
You damn witch.
Yes, what is it?
You.
Why you.
That all?
If you're going to talk about something, the least you can do is know what you're going to say.
Spirit, watch it.
You shouldn't be so reckless.
Oh, great.
Don't snivel like a little baby.
You're a grown man.
I know that, damn it.
But unlike you, Stein, I am a parent.
So to me, this is...
How do I explain it to you?
It's unforgivable.
If a child's own mother abandons him, who else in the world will he be able to turn to?
Yes, exactly.
That's what I've been trying to say all along.
In any case, we're definitely going to defeat her.
That's pretty much been the plan this whole time.
What should I do now that I'm here?
Right here.
This is my area.
I'm drawing the line to mark it.
But what should I do now?
Kicking up sand doesn't seem to do me any good.
And there's not much else besides sand in this place.
Even the sun is lifeless.
It's just hanging there asleep in the sky.
Doing nothing is probably the best plan.
Hey.
My name is Krona.
Of course.
It always shows up when I'm doing nothing.
Can I ask you some questions?
Here goes.
And here we go with the questions again.
When all I really want to do is nothing.
Can I pass if I want?
That's up to you, I guess.
Here are my questions.
First question.
What's your name?
I pass.
That was an easy one.
You mean you won't even say what your name is?
Why do you think that is?
I pass.
Here, let me see if I can answer that one for you.
Basically, you can't answer other people's questions.
So you question yourself in order to keep your mind intact.
Sound about right?
Pass.
Another pass?
You need to start answering.
This isn't even self-questioning at this point.
Wouldn't you agree?
Pass.
Are you hoping someone will start paying attention to you if you act troubled enough?
But don't you realize you're alone?
That no one actually cares about your suffering?
I pass.
That makes five passes.
Let's change the subject, then.
We can talk about the little one.
When you beat it up, that was your first time.
How did you feel after you defeated it?
Pass.
It must have been refreshing, huh?
Finally finding an opponent weaker than you?
Pass.
That's how you felt, isn't it?
And that's why you didn't question Lady Medusa when she told you to become more powerful.
Pass.
You've grown very strong since that first time.
How does that make you feel?
I pass.
Has that made it better?
Has it helped drive away the hell inside your head?
I pass.
Just answer a question already, will you?
Otherwise, won't the hell grow even larger?
I pass.
41 passes.
That's 41 times that you've denied me.
You're a horrible person.
The worst.
You've never said anything mean like that to me before.
Why do you have to keep hanging around me anyway?
Because of you, everyone around me gets hurt.
And so do I.
I wish you didn't exist.
What?
Do you think I'm some kind of alter ego you have?
I thought surely you'd know better than to believe that by now.
Don't you get it?
I'm an ordinary emotion that everybody has.
But you'd rather believe something else.
It's just that...
You don't know how to deal with others?
Repeating that is exactly how you've ended up in this state of self-denial.
Where are you trying to go?
I pass.
You know, I think we've had enough of this.
I'm going on ahead.
Forty-two.
My name's Maka.
I'm a scythe-meister.
Tell me who you are.
Demon swordsman Krona.
Why was I able to answer the question that time?
I am the demon swordsman Krona.
I know that.
Huh?
Hello?
Can I come in there, too?
No, you can't.
Stay back.
Huh?
Why not?
No one can come inside the line I drew.
This is my area.
It's just for me.
Why's that?
I don't understand.
Oh, no.
This is bad.
How can you come inside here so easily?
No one should be able to get past my line.
A line, huh?
I don't know how to deal with other people,
so I feel better when I'm safe in here all by myself.
Now it's ruined.
It won't work anymore.
Not with you here.
But look, it's so easy to erase.
No!
Stop it!
Please don't erase my circle!
All right.
All gone.
What now?
A blood rejection?
Sol!
Maka!
Pull me out of the madness and you better move quickly!
No way!
Hang on!
Where are you?
Maka!
I'm coming!
It's so thick!
Damn it!
How's Corona?
We made it.
Hey, what are you doing?
I need you to wait here a minute, Sol.
You'll be skewered if you get close to him.
Don't be so frightened.
It's okay.
You're just a little shaken up now that the line you had drawn is a rage.
It's okay, really.
I promise you.
Now I understand it.
Your soul wavelength.
It's not that you don't know how to deal with people.
It's that no one ever took the time to deal with you.
It's all right now.
I've already been given up on plenty of times anyway.
I understand.
I'm not needed for anything anymore.
That's why I decided just now that it would be best for me to disappear.
What do you say?
Will you let me be your friend, Krona?
Please say you will.
I know.
Really?
But I still don't know how to deal with other people.
I know.
The fear of interacting with other people, huh?
Even I get that one.
Girls on,求めるのは完璧なスタイル
いつか歯車のように全てが重なるように
神様いるなら聞いてよ いついつまでも
この瞬間ピートできない毎日を見送らなくちゃ
だからあともう少しだけって
子供でいたい Boys and Girls
何人もこのように隠れひっそ
では夢を見ているっていうストーリー
ご視聴ありがとうございました
Damn, they're fast.
How are we going to catch them?
I know.
This situation calls for these
super fast jet engine sneakers Professor Stein invented
Super fast jet engine sneakers?
What kind of design is this?
It's just a bunch of junk patched together
Don't look at me.
I didn't invent them.
Just put them on already
Hold on.
These have been tested, right?
Here goes.
Ready for liftoff
They exploded, of course
On the next episode of Soul Eater
The seal shrine
The immortal man's tricks
Symmetry is perfection